hi guys welcome back to another episode
of two hot takes I'm your host Morgan
I'm Justin and I'm Lauren you've been
asking for stories that [__] you up mhm
you wanted crazy you wanted out there
who you yeah Oh I thought we were
talking about the fan base no I I me
Lauren I literally will listen to yours
and Allandra and I'm like oh my God and
I'm in my car and I'm like listen here
honey pretending I'm like
op you're like getting the mild ones
yeah but I mean Lauren wants the hot
seat she wants she wants the heat yeah
just a little bit this the hot seat but
it's always funny because it's so much
easier to form your thoughts about the
stories when you're
not like on the podcast yeah everything
seems to make sense cuz whenever I'm
driving sometimes I'll literally turn my
radio off or my podcast off and I say my
response out loud and I'm like wow I
nailed that one yeah even when it's the
one you already were on you already
responded I literally do the same thing
I think it's it's crazy too because I'll
be listening to like an episode the
morning it comes out just like kind of
like proof checking again and I'll be
like wait God I should have said this
right here like ah it would have been
perfect it would have been so good or
like on YouTube I like read the comments
a lot on YouTube to like respond to
people and like have conversations on
there and someone would be like wait
what if he actually had the bag of IDs
because it was something to do with sex
trafficking and I'm
like maybe he's not a murderer maybe
he's a sex trafficker like there's stuff
you don't think about and I'm like 100%
And my opinions Chang too like the more
I learn about some of these stories MH
or like new information I get from
people in the community like engaging on
you know whatever I feel like I'm like
wait okay I'm more educated now yeah but
then when then when we're on with your
dad it's he'll be so adamant about a
point and he'll keep bringing it up
until we argue it until the very end and
then he'll be like well maybe it is that
I know he's just very he's very positive
very just like full of wisdom and I
think that's like a great um like
opposite of me who I'm like I'm I kind
of go the more pessimistic route with
these people because I I read too much
on Reddit and I you've seen some [__]
I've seen some [__] um so there's that
but these stories today you wanted
[__] wild and I hope I'm going to
deliver because this episode theme is
unhinged let's do it okay let's dive
[Music]
in so I actually mentioned this story on
all Hunter episode The mother-in-laws
and Mom's episode and I mentioned it in
regards to a listener wrri in and The
Listener was basically like my
mother-in-law we went to a wedding
recently and she kept introducing us in
a weird way and she kept saying this is
my son this is my daughter-in-law and
this is my baby and kept pointing to her
belly and I was like it sounded familiar
to another Reddit story so I went in my
archives dug it up so that's the one
that's up first but I do want to say you
know we had a lot of positive comments
on the YouTube that were like maybe it's
a cultural thing like maybe she's being
really nice blah blah blah blah so that
being said I get some mother-in-laws are
very nice and just very friendly but
this story is what gave me my uncomfy
vibes and heie
chibies okay you ready we're ready very
ready my stepmom tried to walk out of my
home with her baby and told me she
doesn't need permission to leave with
her baby and it wasn't her
baby God damn it she married my dad when
I was 15 and even though being 25 years
age Gap she was more of an older sister
and friend rather than a parent we
remained like this for a couple years
and I looked up to her a lot then the
trouble started i' had only been with my
boyfriend for 2 and 1/2 years before I
found out I was pregnant not only were
we happy but my in-laws and my dad were
happy for us as well my stepmom wasn't
the excuses started I was too young I
wasn't married this wasn't an
environment for the baby to grow up in
she also wanted custody of our baby and
wasn't happy when we told her we would
be raising this baby this went on for a
while we were no contact with her for a
month that was when my dad fully spoke
to her and let her know her actions and
words need to be kept to themselves we
were adults we could make our own
decisions she did apologize to us and
promised to stop we gave her another
chance she had never done this before
and she could have been afraid for us
but we told her that we would be fine
and always had things planned out if
things changed in a heartbeat she seemed
fine for a couple of weeks but then
behind my back she was pushing my
boyfriend to propose by this point we
were at the start of quarantine his
parents were stuck at our house as they
couldn't fly home and my boyfriend
eventually decided that instead of
telling me this he went to his mom who
always wore the family engagement ring
and asked for it so he could propose I
caught on when mother-in-law
accidentally let it slip I sat my
boyfriend down and told me that he knew
we had discussed marriage before and
both agreed we were happy and how things
were in our relationship at the moment
he agreed but told me what my stepmom
told him I wasn't happy and after
talking to my dad she received a massive
lecture from him she called to apologize
and to say she was just looking out for
me I told her thank you but we were fine
I definitely kept my guard up after that
we had our son in August and my dad and
stepmom stood at the edge of our front
porch while we stood by the front door
so they could see him my stepmom kept
trying to come near the baby which is
where I would step back while my
boyfriend would block her while my dad
grabbed my stepmom she kept apologizing
saying she kept forgetting but for a
week after that she was constantly
texting every day wanting to see the
baby my dad eventually made her stop
after I told him and I think um the
context of this is like it was really
really early on in Co and so they wanted
to like keep her and everyone else away
from the baby yeah wait and also I I
miss this how old are they now there's
been no mention of age so far we saw her
on Christmas she wanted to constantly
hold him even went into his Nursery as
he slept and tried to pick him up as he
slept we always saw this on the monitors
and yelled up the stairs for her to
leave him this led to a fight and she
left with my dad I know they had a
massive fight because Dad told me her
reaction was something he had never seen
she had a miscarriage before they met
and her first marriage fell apart
because of it he thinks this has sparked
up old memories for her he promised to
get her some help the moment he got back
from his work trip my boyfriend works
with my dad so he left too I've been
mostly alone with the baby all week
yesterday my stepmom wanted to come by
to pick up something I left her alone to
get what she needed from my garage I
left my office door open while I worked
and could see the baby who was on the
floor in the living area my stepmom was
taking forever so I went to check on her
she wasn't out by her car so I took the
baby and looked around the house for her
I found her in my son's Nursery packing
up some of clothes I asked her what she
was doing and she told me she was taking
the baby for a couple days I told her
she didn't ask for permission nor was
she taking him that's when she got angry
looked straight at me and said I don't
need permission to take my
baby I told her he wasn't her baby and
she needed to leave or else I'd call the
police she continued to pack and ignored
me so I went to grab my phone she Then
followed me down the stairs screaming at
me she was leaving but tried to grab my
baby in the process when she realized
she wasn't going to get him she screamed
at me saying she only wanted to kiss him
goodbye before leaving oh
okay I told you're trying to kidnap a
baby and then you're mad that they won't
let you kiss
goodbye I told my boyfriend and dad and
I know things didn't go well for her and
my dad because she's now telling me that
if I hadn't gotten pregnant it wouldn't
be causing problems in her
marriage yeah what is wrong with
her this is truly this is mental illness
to me like when I first read this one
I'm like this sounds like a serious
episode of like psychosis this but how
did this happen like she I don't know
this just out of how did just that spark
it like how is there nothing bab I know
like is was there any other signs it
sounds like everyone was besties and
then this happened it sounds like the
start to a horror film
honestly just like coming in like this
is my baby yeah just packing everything
up and running out do you guys watch
manifest a little bit yeah not fully
through it oh you have to get to the end
and this will spark some things for some
people all right yeah some crazy baby
stealing happening yeah I I think um
there's a couple more stories that we're
going to read that are kind of similar
to this you guys but I think there is
just something that past traumas and
like tension really comes up when people
have babies so crazy but it like
completely took over her she it's like
she was on autopilot she's really
enveloped in this baby now it's her baby
this is the story though when I heard
the one with Alandra I was like oh like
and a lot of people have written in
since and been like my parents I live at
home with my parents and they constantly
call my baby their baby and it's almost
making me feel like my baby is my
sibling oh my gosh like it's making me
feel so weird and uncomfortable and I'm
like oh my God yeah like language is
just like so important it's like oh like
my little grandbaby like it's just well
it is kind of weird too cuz I think
about um I mean my sister had my niece
at a young age and and she ended up
living with us for a little bit and my
mom absolutely was not like this is my
child or anything like that but you know
my mom went into like her mom mode you
know cuz that's what she's known for her
past four kids so like she would help
out and be like very motherly you know
to but that's a grandma role but yeah it
is a grandma role but but we all live
together so I think it just like
sometimes it was annoying to my sister
because kind of blur yeah cuz it's like
okay know your place Grandma I got I got
this yeah but so I think that can get
confusing when you do have a um a baby
and you're living with your parents when
they're so young you know cuz the
grandma is it's like they go on to like
this mode where they're like I'm going
to help and take care and all this and
like when they're all living together
then it can make the mother be like all
right let's uh chill out yeah this is
definitely not that rational grandparent
stepping in Behavior though this is not
at all
completely just this mental illness like
this is out of this world not normal
yeah this is some crazy [__] well I had
I had this one thought while you were
talking about this and I don't
know or I don't actually think this
would be the case but like in a crazy
world what if the Stepmom was hooking up
with the baby daddy still didn't come
out of her yeah but still you're not
going to be like this is mine no no no I
know but I'm
saying wait it doesn't work like that
what um no but I'm just saying that like
she could be so attached potentially to
like the baby daddy that she was like
this should have been my baby kind of
thing update update update no official
update I'll um I'll read the top
comments and then I'll read some top
comments or I'll read some comments from
op so the top comment does not seem like
rational Behavior at all please have a
talk with your support system and make
sure they all understand that this is
serious you need to protect your family
and her husband needs to get her medical
attention that she so clearly needs be
safe um thank God the dad is on the side
because what like you know how some like
they like no you're lying you're wrong
gasl support pick the wife side I
completely agree like to have the dad be
like no like get in line this isn't
normal like he's constantly reprimanding
her I think is very very very refreshing
yeah I agree um next comment yikes you
may want to make a police report or have
it documented in some way she also
probably should not be left around the
baby at all under any circumstances I'm
so sorry you're going through this very
very supportive like you might want to
get a restraining order your stepmom
needs professional help because yeah
this it really does sound like her
miscarriage seriously affected her and
it's almost like some PTSD really like
coming to light and being
triggered um so some comments from
op I know I'm already talking to a
lawyer and my in-laws have agreed to go
with me to go to the police I'll be
doing that first thing in the
morning um wow
yeah well at least she has all the
support around her yeah but still it's
just like forever now you're just
constantly thinking well I have a
feeling what's going to happen is they
their marriage might not work
out sorry but sorry go on constantly
thinking what Justin oh I don't know I
just like initially when it when she was
first saying it I just thought if it
happened to me if I'm in that situation
I almost think when she first says that
you're almost kind of like ha yeah like
okay nobody told me and you kind of
think it's a joke or something but then
when she's like freaking out then it
becomes scary almost and then it is the
restraining order or yeah but it just
sucks to even have to involve law
enforcement into Family Matters like
that it's just so weird it's very common
though no I know it is it's so no I'm
not saying it's weird in this like
overall it's just if you were in that
situation it just feels very weird to
have to call the police on your
mother-in-law and just go through that
cuz then forever that's just kind of a
strained it's not weird relationship you
have it's not ideal and like my family
has gone through some [__] like my
brother one of the first times you met
my brother he talked about like a fight
he had gotten into with my other
siblings biological dad and I don't
think the cops were ever called on that
and like my mom I've witnessed some like
abuse from partners with my mom and like
the cops were never called on that but
like they definitely should have so it's
like I wish they would have been but
even even though they weren't those
things still last forever they do like
that trauma sticks with you it's
obviously it's it still affects me it's
shaped me it shapes the way I look at
relationships and I think that's where a
lot of my opinions come from it's like
witnessing trauma and experiencing
trauma like that I guess like let's
leave off like there's been no updates
on this lady this post is 7 months old
there was never an official update after
there's only comments on the account and
no post afterwards wow so hope she's
okay hope she's
okay
um I would assume that it was handled
very well it sounds like she's got a
great support system
and I think it'll be okay for her yeah
yeah I would oh sorry go no I was just
going to say cuz if if there was some
other crazy [__] that went down you'd
think it would end up back on here I'm
really surprised she did not update
because of the fact she was very
responsive in the
comments but maybe like it is also hard
like once you get a lawyer involved they
don't want you speaking out and I think
a lot of people on Reddit don't update
because of the seriousness of you know
everything that's going on yeah yeah I
mean I would cuz my thought is that
either the husband is going to help his
wife get some help or she'll help
herself I mean it me needs to obviously
happen from her um and if she doesn't
husband probably has no choice than to
leave her and then if he leaves her then
is this woman really still going to be
attached to her like ex stepdaughter's
baby well she going to start stalking
her yeah then it gets really I mean that
would be really scary but I feel like
the fixation is almost because they are
like so intertwined yeah but who knows
okay
so if you're listening to the
podcast you will miss my dad's hello but
tune in on YouTube to see his his cute
waa
shirt also that pizza that your dad is
making smells so good yeah wait do you
have any extra
Pizza hello
Dad yeah come say hi come say hi I look
how he only responds to whistles come
say
hi come say hi come say hi yeah yeah oh
my God what are you wearing yeah this is
perfect here this is perfect come say hi
remember when you guys played uh that
pong game on your from two different
back got to duck a little bit so I can
see your outfit oh I supposed to duck
yeah you got duck down down there you go
now you're in the view show them your
avocado again
avocado beautiful and the shirs love oh
my gosh he's literally wearing a gas
station like shirt Wawa it's a gas
station where did he get that I know I
feel like those are just out east
they're in like Florida I think too my
Uncle Jimmy is a big fan of waa I'd say
Florida's East yeah it yeah it's east of
where we are but like I don't know
florid is in its own little boat they're
so wild uh so up
next there's two kidnapping stories jeez
wow I'm telling you you
guys kidnapping babies is really common
apparently that's
terrifying up first the time my mom k
kidnapped our newborn is the
title to preface this the incident
happened exactly 1 year ago today we are
no contact with my parents and will be
for the foreseeable future unless my mom
gets therapy my doing wife and I are in
therapy but not so much because of the
issues we have in our marriage but
because we both have shitty families and
neither of us until meeting our
therapist had strong spines we are very
low contact with wife's mother she's
more becc than anything but she also has
some drug issues she's dealing with
namely an addiction to painkillers what
is BEC
there's a lot of terms on just no
mother-in-law and here's where my Reddit
expertise goes down um let's Google it
someone literally posted on just no
mother-in-law and they go what do all
the acronyms mean question exclamation
question exclamation just like down a
line because I love like a lot of the
subreddits when they they abbreviate
things like M M M like mother-in-law
obviously abbreviate it great but just
know mother-in-law is like notorious for
like creating these new [__] it's
like the little text things it's so
annoying so someone lit the top comment
on this post I've stopped coming here
often because of all the damn acronyms I
hate acronyms mother-in-law is fine I
don't follow the stories that have a lot
of acronyms so funny it also probably
takes more effort to Think Through It it
would be rather than just type it so
apparently becc is like throughout this
entire thread and
apparently it stands for [__] eating
crackers I was going to guess
that um basically a becc moment or
action is when the person you're talking
about has gotten so fed up that every
little thing they do is annoying
deservedly or not okay so they're just
like they're on your nerve got it
essentially okay let's go back a year in
a few days wife is due any second with
our first child my mom up to this point
has been a [__] eating crackers mostly
little annoying things however she has
also been patronizing of wife in the six
years we were together 2 years married
I've always shut that [__] down but I'll
admit I should have gone low contact or
no contact before this so the plan was
to have both sets of parents to the
hospital after the baby arrived and wife
and I had time to bond her parents
accepted that my dad who is an enabler
was okay with that but my mom was not
she demanded she'd be at the hospital we
told her no she had to wait finally she
said okay after she saw we wouldn't put
our feet down so the baby was born it's
a boy we hadn't found out so it was a
big surprise anyway both sets of parents
come everything's good finally wife is
tired so I walk my parents out hers had
gone home my dad went out to get the car
I waited by the front door with Mom she
turns to me and says that my dad and her
are filing for custody of our
baby she claims my wife is on drugs like
her mom a lie wife doesn't even drink
and that she saw how wife was around the
baby and she fears for his safety I'm
stucked
my dad pulls up and she gets in and
leaves I go back upstairs and my wife
sees my face I really don't want to tell
her but I'm not going to lie to her
she's upset as I am so I text my mom
that she's not to contact us I then
block her number my younger sister is
blowing my phone up and I know it's my
mom I get along great with my little
sister as does wife but she was a minor
at the time and lived with my
folks we go home the next day wife had
taring and therefore needs meds she
refuses pain meds because of family
history but she says she will take Advil
so I go get some things at CVS wife and
baby are sleeping him and his C in line
getting us dinner when wife calls
hysterical she woke up and no baby oh my
God I run home and we are both a mess at
this time then my neighbor comes over
and she says what's going on she sees me
running like my feet are on fire so I
tell her she tells me wait so your
parents weren't supposed to take the
baby yep my mom came and kidnapped my
baby wow I call the Sheriff's Office my
best friend is a deputy there as soon as
I tell him and his partner what happened
they had to get our baby turns out my
dad wasn't involved in the actual
kidnapping although I'm sure he knew
about it my mom knew at the time where
we kept a spare key and let herself in
both her and her FM were arrested
because there wasn't a chance in hell we
weren't pressing charges the baby was
returned to us and according to my
friend they had a nursery
waiting holy [__] [__] how did the
[__] what's wrong with the dad he's
an enabler but what a psychopath I don't
care if you're an enabler like that's
scary to me because this other woman she
probably has some like severe mental
health issues this dad seems like he's
just like going along with the ride it's
like just as bad as doing it yeah it is
I think enabling in some cases is just
as bad as actually doing it well yeah I
think it's literally if not even worse
cuz like well I'm I'm pretending that
the dad is a little bit more level and
the mom is just like having some serious
issues so like if that's the case then
like how can you in your right [__]
mind watch somebody kidnap someone
else's baby I have a nursery ready a
nursery oh my God the thing the dad
obviously knew the plan it was she's
rearranging a guest bedroom or whatever
an office for a [__] new baby but how
is that ever going to work oh well
actually she could have said like oh I
just want to make sure the baby has a
comfortable place to like stay watch the
baby yeah and he might have been like oh
my wife's being crazy but because she
said she what the be was that right
after she gave birth to the baby
yeah that is so crazy I can't even
imagine like being like after having
birth like having some psychopath like
say this [__] to me to me right but you
have to be nuts to think that that's
actually going to work you're not going
to end up with the
kid yeah what's the point unhinged she's
unhinged and that's the thing like you
her being like Oh I saw how she was with
the baby I'm scared for his safety she
just pushed that thing out Y what how
can you say that that that little baby
is probably hold up in court what do you
mean like all the doctors are around
like she couldn't even abuse that baby
if she desper wanted to you know what I
mean like she like and also who knows
how long her goddamn labor was like she
was potentially pushing exhausted in
labor forever like she's probably so
tired and just wants to bond with her
child and then sleep and then have her
mother-in-law come in and be like yeah
well you can go [__] yourself I'm going
to take your baby and you're just trying
to like recover recuperate you're just
trying to take a little Advil and relax
wait do we have the ages of everyone no
ages in this
post oh my God his username though it is
um not today
Satan I love that it is another horror
film
exorcism I don't know Justin these ones
might [__] you up more than Lauren oh no
it doesn't like I'm not afraid of all
that but I'm just like [__] can you
imagine yeah it's
wild cuz again on the like you have to
now you will not have these people in
your life no if my mom tried to do this
to me I would kick her ass I'm picturing
that it's very
interesting I just can't
imagine I can't imagine any parent in my
life doing that I don't know I mean what
if someone was normal forever and then
it just happened and they spped yeah
well like the one's stepmom they had a
good relationship until they got
pregnant it's like H so he does go on to
say my mom was sentenced but because of
her standing in the community she was
only given a slap on the wrist however
the negative attention she got after
that event spurred her and my dad to
move good thankfully my sister [__]
thankfully my sister turned 18 before
then and she stayed with us a few months
before going a few states away to school
for a long time both her and my dad were
radio silent however my mom has tried to
reach out in the last few months
thankful
thankfully we've learned from this we
have cameras a security system and no
spare key outside our neighbor who is
now a great friend has our spare key we
are 3 months along with our second child
I'm hoping my mom doesn't find out
season 2 neighbor steals baby oh my God
I knew
like can you imagine I know you're no
spare key no spare key I know that
you're just you just had a kid
you're trying to get you know and that
takes up crazy amounts of time and very
stressful in
itself but if I were this couple I would
also move that's what I was thinking I
was surprised they stayed I wouldn't I I
don't know I would just be out yeah so
this guy neighbor has the key he did
move actually now that you mentioned
that really trust the neighbors and he
moved to a gated community that has a
security guard
and has been made aware of the mom so no
worry there W she's going to jump the
bushes yeah what's interesting though is
the story I was between on this one the
title is mother-in-law basically
kidnapped my
baby and it's very very very similar we
had our daughter about four weeks ago
she's been over at least 3 days every
week since we've had her she's always
tell me what I'm doing wrong and how
she'd do things differently baby is up
every 2 hours and she insists she'd
sleep through the night if she could
stay at Grandma's oh yeah so what she
did is they put the baby down to sleep
the two of them went to bed and they
woke up you know 4 hours later and they
were like the baby hasn't woken up yet
what like what is going on the baby
hasn't woken up did she die from SIDS
because that's every you know I feel
like that's at least it would be my fear
but I feel like as a new mom first time
Mom it's a big part of like your fears
is like SIDS and so they go and check on
the baby and it's gone see turns out
turns out the
Mother-in-law stole the key came in and
took the baby yeah and these are the
people you're trying to rely on to help
you in these times of very much need
where you just need an extra hour sleep
or you need a little help here can you
watch the baby just help us out a little
bit and then this [__] happens mhm do
you know what makes me mad about stuff
like this is
that and this could go for a lot of
different situations but this
person was a mother once yeah and and
I'm just like don't you put yourself in
the shoes of when you were a brand new
mother if your mother-in-law or if your
mother did this like like because you
were a mother because you know how that
feels how do you think this is okay I
think they disassociate from their time
out as a mother and it's almost like
there could be I mean there's so many
reasons it could be I think they're
better then I feel like I feel like they
feel entitled to this child I think
maybe there's some mental health things
where I want to do over I want this to
be my baby I see this as my baby I'm
this is just me and I'm right you're
doing it
wrong I mean it's kind of like Justin
said like how maybe you have all these
crazy thoughts but how do you think
you're going to get away with that right
it's never going to happen
unhinged there's more kidnapping stories
I found I'll post the links on the
YouTube description if you guys want to
read them anyways but I think I think
we're good on the the kidnappy kid Vibes
right yeah yeah yeah yeah um give us
some more diversity yeah it sounds like
all these people got it figured out uh
luckily the update on the one where the
Mom stole the key and took the kid while
they were
sleeping um they got it all sorted I'll
post that up date so not actual
kidnapping but this one's still a little
dicey okay am I the [__] for refusing
to attend my brother's wedding after my
sister-in-law left my two-month-old on a
park bench me and my sister-in-law have
always been close her and my brother met
when they were 15 I was 12 and I'm now
21 she was always really nice to me and
we bonded over the fact that my parents
don't like either of us a few weeks ago
I got called in to work and my
sister-in-law said that I shouldn't
waste money on a babysitter when I could
just let them take her for a bit my
husband was also at
work I guess at some point she decided
to take her and her dog for a walk she
says they were walking through the park
and the leash slipped out of her hand
without thinking she put my daughter on
a nearby bench she was in a little
carrier and she ran after the dog she
didn't even catch the dog and it wasn't
until until 2 hours later that she even
realized that she was
missing
okay when I came to pick up my daughter
she broke down and told me everything I
was livid but I was so thankful no one
kidnapped her my husband was so mad he
stormed down to their house just to yell
at her mhm she recently messaged me the
details about her wedding I told her I
would not be attending she called me
sobbing saying that I am a petty [__]
and she wishes someone would have
kidnapped my daughter oh okay that's way
that justifies the decision yeah I was
going to say like At first I could see
just being like forgive me but making
that comment like no [__] you that is
[__] up I hung up on her and she
apologized and said she needs me there
my friends and family have called me
saying I'm Petty and that she was
stressed and it was an accident am I the
a
that's not an
accident that's not an accident I love
love dogs love animals baby dog
two-month-old baby
dog yeah but even if you set the baby
down and 10 seconds later you're like oh
okay that was say that she left the baby
there for 2 hours 2 hours yeah and she
didn't find the dog didn't even get the
dog no got so distracted by looking for
the dog was she drunk probably cuz how
oh my God
so do you want to know where this gets
worse does it trick question can it get
worse it gets worse it gets worse let me
find the comment from op so apparently
like op is again very this one is very
very responsive she goes kidnapping is
quite common in my area but the park is
sort of hidden but still like it's quite
common in her area like that is a
terrifying thought oh my God that's so
terrifying yeah playing with
so someone comments and they go yikes
what was she doing for 2 hours before
she realized she left her on a bench
looking for the dog the whole time
question mark not the [__] and she
goes yeah she said for about 40 minutes
she was looking for the dog then she
told me she went shopping for clothes
for my daughter how can you buy clothes
for someone and not realize
they were supposed to be with you for
the last 2 hours what happened to her
that's insane W that's not even just
spacing out or forgetting that's just
that I don't even know what that is yeah
that is crazy it's like memory loss
seriously I but the thing that the
craziest thought to me about that is is
if I was the
parent I think about the fact that it's
so frustrating that I like when I
misplace my keys I can't just like call
my keys I don't have like a tracker on
them I can't figure out where they are
if someone kidnapped your tiny little
baby you can't just like Ping it oh no
you'd be [__] like what the [__] that
is the most terrifying thing the I can't
I can't imagine and like when you trust
somebody to watch your baby to leave
them in a park by themselves hours for 2
hours what if it was super sunny outside
that's what if it was hot and this baby
literally [__] died from the [__]
elements so scary here I go swearing I
was doing so well no I [__] swear but
but that's the thing didn't Bo say that
he liked how much I swore yeah yeah so
that's the thing it's like what if this
little baby 2 hours for a
two-month-old two Monon old two-month
old babies are they're so little they're
so easily affected by heat and
dehydration so I'm curious if she
realized and then went back to the park
and found her there or if there's
actually other people around cuz if you
I mean if any of us were walking around
and you see just a random baby on a park
bench all of us would run up and be like
all right what is going on here go to
the police station you figure it out so
still but how do you even figure that
out you don't have like a name t on a
baby you know what I mean well still but
at least you it's just so crazy the idea
that like you lose a baby it's like how
do people identify it's just at least
you know that
you have control of the situation in the
sense that something terrible isn't
going to happen but this is just crazy
either the park is not very popular but
still even you're just tempting disaster
yeah
literally well okay the one thing that I
will say is that so she went back and
got the baby before they came home
right that's yeah so so she at least she
admitted to it and she did she
technically like didn't have to say
anything she did come clean so that's
where I'm like okay well at least she's
not yeah so Opie does
go that's admirable no one picked no one
picked the baby up no one sat with the
baby the baby was just sitting there for
2 hours and so op goes I'm sure that
there were a few people in the 2 hours
but no one stopped to get her that's
crazy if I saw an infant on a bench
alone I'd assume its mother was around
the park somewhere but I'd still keep an
eye on it I think it's very strange how
no one stopped
and so she like comments a bunch and
so um she basically says luckily it
wasn't too hot but she's a little
sunburned on her arms we've already
taken her to the doctor SL hosp they
said we shouldn't worry too
much um and a lot of people are just
kind of like is your sister-in-law
jealous of you getting all of this
attention because you had a baby doesn't
sound like it though it doesn't sound
like a jealousy thing I I don't know I
just cuz if it would why like why would
that be a jealousy thing I don't like I
I mean she's getting married and you
know she her sister future sister-in-law
you know thinking not thinking from the
sister-in-law that left the baby's
perspective it's like I'm getting
married I want the B to be on me so you
think she just wanted the attention of
being like look what I did
wrong no but I think she like I think
when people are jealous and insecure of
themselves they self-sabotage or they
try to hurt those individuals that
they're jealous of um for example I read
a story today about this individual who
was insecure about their
friend had felt threatened by this
friend and during a test in school she
put laxatives in her drink and her
sandwich at lunch to sabotage her friend
from taking the test and then if you go
look at that person's profile they also
admit to crushing up sleeping pills and
putting them in their friend's food wow
I think there's unhinged people that
need mental health help but but that's
intention like that like they had a
result that they were looking for where
is this I'm like what result would she
be looking for maybe she wanted the baby
to get kidnapped maybe she wanted to
hurt her in a way but then why wouldn't
she just try again instead of telling
them what she did I mean she left that
child there for 2 hours and went
shopping I know but I'm just saying like
why why didn't she like why would she
tell oh like why versus actually acting
it out again yeah I don't know so I'm
like I like I have no words for this one
I have no idea it doesn't add up like
nothing about it adds so weird but the
fact that when she was confronted by I'm
not going to come to your wedding and
she was like I wish your baby would have
been kidnapped that is some crazy [__]
instead of being like you know what I'm
really sorry I understand I'm hurt I
want you there but I understand like I
say some things that I don't mean when
I'm really hurt but like to bring the
baby in and say I wish your baby got
kidnapped that is not that is not okay
that also but that doesn't surprise me
that much I and I'm not I don't think
leaving the baby there was malicious I
don't think that was for me at least I'm
not seeing that as the intention I think
it's just some person who is either very
forgetful or
just just not all there to the point
where you could forget that heavily
you're distracted by chasing a dog yeah
that you make a dumb Choice and then
realize that later right but even still
you could be that far removed where
you're just like then just dumb and then
then don't commit to watching a
two-month-old baby yeah but but they
also wouldn't be smart enough if they
could make these dumb choices to make
that decision on the front end to say no
so yes obviously going
forward no one's going to trust her with
the baby but I don't I just don't think
she left the baby there on purpose I I I
truly this one has me very baffled same
I don't want to like think she did it
maliciously because how [__] up is
that yeah wouldn't that end up couldn't
that end up being like some sort of
crime yeah I mean I don't even know I
think I I think even now she could get
charges pressed against her for neglect
yeah I was going to say even the the one
that you had with Alejandra the story
where like the the grandma left the
2-year-old I mean there's reckless
endangerment there's and but it was like
neglect too she just left the child to
go do laundry there's so many crazy laws
that I I mean even lawyers don't know
about there's so many crazy laws and
just specifics that you could probably
press charges for which she does mention
in one of her comments she gives like an
update she's like I didn't think this
post would really blow up they always
say that I have agreed to go to the
wedding if my brother can send if my
brother chooses to follow through with
the wedding my sister and I are trying
to even him to just reconsider the
wedding and take a second to actually
think about what's happening I'm
seriously thinking about getting the
police
involved yeah but so someone made a
comment and this is why I'm like I don't
think there's any health issues
involved um but someone made a comment
they're like not the [__] but have
you talked to your brother about this
was he not concerned that his fiance
left his baby niece alone for 2 hours
right also consider the fact that this
isn't just your sister-in-law's wedding
it's your brother's wedding so maybe if
you want you can just go in support of
your brother not your sister-in-law if
you don't feel comfortable with that
it's perfectly fine because you are
entitled to how you feel and she goes
yeah I talked to my brother and he
excused it by saying quote she's got
diagnosed high blood pressure me and my
older sister are trying to talk to him
about reconsidering the engagement this
is so far just so unrelated and yes it
is a tangent but I feel like
we as people every day make just stupid
mistakes that are pretty forgetful like
one time I went into Chipotle and left
the keys in my car with my car running
the whole time I was in there just not
thinking mhm and I came out and I was
like what how did this happen like how
did I make this mistake and you almost
just you don't even understand what
happened and I wasn't drunk I wasn't
anything well and so you just think like
and yes a baby is a whole new ball game
but but I think you can still make weird
forgetful mistakes especially if you're
and it also isn't her kid too so I can I
don't know I don't know what I'm trying
to say but so I have the perfect thing I
mean in the United States
alone the stats of babies dying in cars
every year is horrendous M wow I mean
parents and one of the most like tragic
pictures I've ever seen on on the
internet was a parent who left his child
in the car when he went into work forgot
to drop the baby off at daycare and the
baby died in the car so sad and it's
just like
forgetfulness he typically didn't bring
the baby to daycare his wife did so he
forgot to drop the baby off he deviated
from his routine it wasn't it you know
he was so locked in his patterns and his
behavior and it's like you know for the
sister-in-law she probably doesn't watch
the baby a lot the baby's only 2 months
old so you know for her her pattern and
her routine is going to the park [__]
her dog ran away I got to think about
the dog and then it's like out of sight
out of mind that's my thought I think
the confusing thing cuz all of this I
could see it happening the confusing
thing to me is like how do you just lose
a dog and you're like H I'm just going
to go shopping now yeah did she find the
dog like you said she didn't even find
the dog so like I would think that if I
lost my dog after 40 minutes of looking
for my dog I would be like I'm going to
start making posters I'm going to go to
like the police or like the the vet or
what what whatever I can do to just like
be like hey this is a picture of my dog
please everyone look for this like the
fact that like it was like 40 minutes
and you're like well time to go shopping
that's where I'm kind of confused she
just seems off yeah she's off um I
looked through the comments there's no
mention of her even finding the dog the
only comment related to the dog was yeah
she said she was looking for the dog for
about 40 minutes so no idea um sounds
like this one is still really developing
D very interesting yeah there's no
official update yet and the last comment
was basically we're trying to get my
brother to reconsider I would say that
that's kind of invasive and I don't you
know like if she genuinely it was such
an accident and she's so like remorseful
then like for you to be like trying to
break up her marriage um but the fact
I'm sure there's other stuff going on
I'm sure this isn't the only thing I'm
sure this is like and the fact and it's
a huge thing too so it's not a small
thing but like if it was genuinely such
an accident you know um but the fact
that she said I wish your baby would
have gotten kidnapped that's the one
that sticks with me I'm like how could
you say that to somebody true [__] yeah
ABS that's and people lash out when
they're embarrassed or hurt I get I
that's you know we all do it but it's so
easy to just Rectify a situation or like
the last thing you want to do is stir
the boat more the easiest way that you
could rectify this it's like you know
what I'm really sorry I did this I I
completely understand sorry what is stir
the boat a phrase oh it's stir the
pot okay sorry go on but yeah like you
just got to smooth things over it's like
I know I [__] up I'm so sorry I
respect your decision I'm going to give
you your space yeah first says I wish
your daughter would have been kidnapped
yeah that's [__] up like if she would
have just been like you're a petty [__]
fine whatever she's mad she's hurt she
feels
embarrassed she crossed the line without
how the rest of the family on the wife's
side my friends and family have called
me saying I'm Petty and that she was
stressed why is the rest of the family
on her side CU we don't know what story
she's telling probably the sister-in-law
or all of them we don't know if what
she's telling us is completely
everything yeah yeah maybe they were all
in on
it just wild conspiracies oh let's not
even go about that well you guys love
[Laughter]
that what was that sound effect I was
trying I was trying to copy your go and
then it it it was like even more
powerful than I thought you sounded like
an animated cartoon it was out of
control it literally sounds like it's
outside of the headphones like I feel
like it's all around us okay well I'm
going to take a little bathroom break
okay same uh I guess same so up next am
I the [__] for not wanting to give my
late husband's sperm to his
parents I'm sorry I really tried to
think of a less silly title when my
husband was diagnosed with cancer we
froze his sperm so we could have
children via insemination even after
chemotherapy his parents were very
involved in his treatment and were aware
that we were doing this his treatment
was unfortunately unsuccessful and he
passed away on July
19th his parents asked me if I was
considering being inseminated with his
sperm and I said no then they asked me
if I could transfer ownership of the
sperm to them so they could use it to
have
grandchilden I assume they're planning
on hiring a surrogate for this but I'll
admit I was so surprised and confused I
didn't actually ask my gut reaction was
that this is wrong an exploitative and
not what my husband would have wanted we
froze his sperm because we wanted to
raise a family together and freezing his
sperm seemed like a better option than
adopting or using a sperm donor not
because he wanted to give his parents
grandkids or just put his DNA out into
the world for the sake of it I'm so
confused about who they expect to raise
this child or children as they're both
in their 60s the surrogate question mark
one of their nieces or
nephews my husband has no siblings and I
certainly wouldn't feel comfortable
doing it it feels like they just want
their bloodline to continue without any
thought to the practicality of
it that's probably what it is I'm
actually kind of torn on this one I look
at this and I really
to put this into
perspective he died July 19th this post
was 6 days ago so it was technically
written on either July 31st or August
1st wow no there's only a there's only
been about two weeks since this man's
death but I think that's part of it I
think his parents are mourning so here's
the thing so if you look at the stages
of grief
anger bargaining guilt you know all the
stages of grief I think they're at the
bargaining stage I think they're at like
okay he's gone but what can I do to have
a piece of him yeah yeah what like what
can I do to bring him back I think
that's where they're at too I but the
thing is is that like if the child has a
great home to be raised in I don't think
there's anything wrong with that I mean
the other thing she's going to do is
just throw the sperm away so it's like
but the the wrong part is that he never
agreed to it so it's like if that would
have been a conversation before he
passed there would be no no question but
because it's like without his consent it
feels really weird it feels wrong well
the wife the wife is going to have the
sense of she's going to have more of the
sense of what he would have wanted than
the parents will I agree with that if
like honestly if she's uncomfortable
with it that's her choice but I think
she would at the end of the day it
almost feels like she should be the one
making this choice but then you also
have to take into consideration that
she's also mourning
so maybe the idea too of him having a
child out there that's not with her is
like horrible you know well and I I
don't see this being a like logical
thing I think they were together they
were married in the reality that was
their reality before he passed they were
together they either planned on having
kids together or not at all I I do I do
think I
and this is a really really hot take
that people have like I've seen on the
internet and has like kind of been
implanted in me now it's like you
shouldn't have a kid because you're
lonely you shouldn't have a kid because
you want a Mini Me Like There's hot
takes that people put out there where
it's like these are reasons why you
shouldn't have a kid and it's like for
these grandparents it's like you
shouldn't have a kid to try to bring
your dead son back yeah because what is
that kid's life going to be that kid's
life is not going to know his parents
yeah and who's going to be the mom who
are they going to get a donor egg that
they don't know where it came from and
then implant that into a surrogate or
like she said maybe a niece like yeah
what is this child's life going to look
like yeah it definitely like if I had to
pick it doesn't feel right it really
just doesn't feel right but I mean it
it's not it's not so awful like if he
were to if they were to continue his DNA
and you know they brought an amazing
human into this world
like I mean once the human gets here
like everyone's going to be so happy and
in love like whoever the like people are
that are taking care of this child but
um at the same time like if this was
never even an idea that floated through
his head then I don't it just doesn't
feel fair to him I'm kind of sad they
mentioned the Frozen sperm to his
parents mhm because if that would have
just been a conversation between them
this dilemma wouldn't have even happened
and I think honestly should have been
that's what I'm saying like I don't
think they should have even like
involved the parents and been like yeah
we're freezing his spur well that's not
even part of the treatment that's a
decision that's like a smart decision
you make as a couple because you're
going to go through this this recovery
process yeah well I um I had a friend in
high school that he got TSC cancer
literally like a year out of high school
and so I remember hearing about the fact
that like they froze some sperm just in
case and blah blah blah and like
that's a decision you make as a couple
but like I don't know I I've also seen a
lot of posts on Reddit that are like my
husband is terminally ill and everyone's
asking me if I'm going to get pregnant
and it's
like why you're already dealing with the
loss of somebody and and then to come in
and raise what would have been your
child together would make it even that
much harder I think for a lot of people
that's
heartbreaking but then I think there are
some some people that are like I'm so
thankful that I do have a piece of my
husband or my partner left and this one
is probably one of the tougher ones like
ethically morally that we've like really
I think what I would do if I was her is
that I would just respond to the parents
and being like I'm mourning I'm sure
that you guys are mourning and this is
not a good time to have a conversation
about that um we can definitely talk
about this but not right now I I think
we need to this has been two weeks since
he passed exactly that's what I'm saying
like we need to we need to heal more
like we're in a really vulnerable moment
all of us and we need to heal more
before we have this conversation and
then at that point like you know if the
parents are like have some really like
compelling reason if they're like he
always said that he wanted to pass like
you know whatever like what and like if
they're really so convincing that
they're like look at his diary as a kid
and this is what I don't know whatever
whatever convers yeah I think the wife
probably knows and I think the right
answer is probably just no but if
there's some you know after they're not
in the thick of mourning if there's some
really genuine reason what where it
makes sense then they can decide but
right now I would be like we all need
space we all need to think about this
yeah and I think that's rational like
you should not make any major life
decisions after a great loss like this
but even still let the dust settle but I
think if he didn't explicitly say
anything about having a kid regardless
of if he's here or not it goes away I
age so I got a lot of comments
op like I'm going to show you guys this
is a throwaway account this is me
scrolling to the
bottom and this is me scrolling all the
way up to the top op comments
extensively little behind the scenes
here extensively we just saw behind the
curtain I know wizard style so I'm going
to try to like do them the best I can I
really want to do this one Justice
because I think this is like probably
one the hardest post we've ever read and
I want to just I'm like want to cry at
this like this is probably for me I just
I can't imagine losing your partner like
this and having to deal with like his
parents coming out of the woodwork two
weeks later and being like hey that
sperm I just lost my son but hey that's
sperm well and it's it's even sad enough
to to need to make the choice to free
sperm in that situation because you know
there's a risk yeah and then to have it
actually happen it's just
I don't know yeah there's one comment I
want to start
with the comment I want to read is in
reply to something else so I kind of
feel like I have to read the comment
from an outside Source first so this
person goes damn I don't even know what
to judge this one I can see most sides
since as of the moment I haven't come to
a definite decision that I can't expect
to say if one of you is the [__] over
the other not the [__] to start I
understand completely why you feel the
way you do and I'm terribly sorry for
your loss I have a couple questions
though did you and your husband actually
decide what he wanted to do in this case
or are you speculating but obviously you
have the authority now are you keeping
it from his parents because you feel
they're yours and only yours so no one
else can have them and you decided you
won't use them deciding what someone
else should be doing with their lives is
not your right so using that to justify
not giving them it is sort of assholery
in that case they love their son I'm
presuming and raising a child that
shares their son's DNA while teaching
the kid about his father and history
doesn't seem so bad the grandparents are
[__] for not being as sensitive as
to you as they should be by asking so
soon however at the same time if they're
in their 60s then they don't have much
time to lose anyway and they might be
thinking that by you deciding against
you using them you're going to move on
from him somehow grief is weird I think
the priority is what would your husband
want mhm but if you or them honestly
don't know if he wanted to pass on his
lineage or whatever reason then it's a
me versus the in-laws question over what
each party wants and yes legally you
have the authority of course but being
an [__] isn't only judged on
legalities the context is key again
sorry for your loss and all the grief so
long- winded great points that was a
pretty good post it it it was very
probing which I appreciate cuz I think
these are all questions that we just
said like what would the husband really
want MH so op goes on to say my aversion
to their plan is due to what I know
about why he wanted to freeze his sperm
he wanted to be a father specifically he
wanted to raise kids with me I know it
wasn't about just passing on his genes
because both adoption and sperm donors
were also options we discussed and he
was fine with those
possibilities I just can't imagine he'd
be comfortable with having a child with
his DNA out there who neither he nor I
had any hand in raising yep yeah and on
top of that too like who he's mixing his
DNA with like not being able to decide
that yeah you know like he didn't get to
pick like okay if I die like I would
want my my DNA to be passed down to this
human or that human it's just like
bringing a child into this
world is a serious
decision I don't like I think you know
unplanned pregnancies happened and
everyone makes the best of that
situation and obviously people are
typically I should say are very happy to
have a child but he's gone like this
autonomy and this decision is
gone so to just assume or to let his
parents just take over the sperm and
like not really know what's going to
happen to it I don't think is it
definitely doesn't seem like it's what
he would have wanted yeah mhm and I'm
I'm trying to put myself in the
situation of him like if I were to die
and had like my eggs saved whatever
would I be that mad if my parents
decided to like pass down my DNA I don't
know so it's so hard to say because he's
not here and like the decision is in him
you know right and it's it's obviously
not going to affect him in any way at
this point but that's true but you want
to honor the person that everyone loves
that H pass away so that's right and my
gut feeling I still feel even a little
bit weird about it if they didn't have
the explicit conversation yeah but I
feel like it should be her or nobody
exactly I agree with that I think where
I'm getting really caught up with this
one is I'm not so much concerned about
the people that are trying to make this
decision like the grandparents AKA like
his parents and the wife okay like yeah
they're affected clearly like they're
directly involved right now but I look
at this child and I don't know if this
is from me having known people that are
adopted and constantly feel this like
burning aching desire like what about my
birth mom like I love my parents that
raised me but what what about my birth
mom why did she give me up right they
there's something to be said about you
know children that go through this
experience of not knowing their birth
parents who they feel a part of them is
missing and there's a lot of trauma with
that I just look at this I'm like it's
just such an unfair situation to bring a
kid into for selfish reasonings of my
son is gone I want a piece of my son it
to me this seems so selfish right and or
continuing the lineage any reason that
the grandparents have is to me is
selfish because it's like no matter what
you do your son is gone MH yeah and I'm
so sorry about that and it's so tragic
but to bring a child into the world to
appease
you what that is really an interesting
concept to think about like the
grandparents like are they like who is
raising them are they raising them and
if they are 60 yeah I have 60-year-old
patients that die every day what are you
going to what where's this one-year-old
going to go is family automatically
going to take him on take her them on
like what it have to be the mom or the
wife I mean but however I will say
um I I mean even when people are adopted
like and they're wondering about their
birth parents I think a part of that is
because they know their birth parent is
out there you know or they don't know
anything about them or something like
that like I think I don't I think it
would be different if you're like I know
that my dad died and this was my
situation you know um because he' be he
would be able to learn about him the
grandparents are going to tell him all
about him you know yeah but I um but I
guess like even still growing up and
hearing about your dad and not having
your dad that's
a it's traumatic either way course it's
not a ideal situation and I mean the
only thing I will say though is that
with a lot of situations it's not ideal
like there's things from my childhood
that I'm like damn like I could have
been like a cooler person if this didn't
happen or whatever it is and I it's just
like life is crazy so I don't I think
more of this story is just really
focusing on like the wife yeah and like
what she wants to decide and like if she
thinks that that's kind of [__] up and
crossing the line she's not the [__]
like it's not the [__] at all for
this
and so with that being said someone
comments I hope you decide to have his
child I'd be the same it's not theirs to
use and she goes me carrying his child
isn't really on the table yeah he's gone
yeah and I feel like for her he's gone
there's no bringing him back then the
sperm should be gone don't deal I agree
I
think he's
gone as
you wanted to raise a kid with her it
would be such a hard place to be put in
though like I'm just picturing if I had
people that loved the person that I
loved
like as or like you know so strongly too
and they were just so desperate and I
was the one who had to make the call to
like break their heart like and you know
what I mean like I I'm sure she's just
feeling so crazy right now or like just
so torn and like well it's so fresh yeah
two weeks you guys like again like two
weeks she just lost her life partner
someone who she they were actively
planning to have a life and kids
together I can't even imagine like
typing this all out and thinking
coherently like yeah I feel like Clarity
will come with time yeah I really do
yeah and again it's been about two weeks
like sit on it don't make any rash
decisions like I saw somewhere where you
shouldn't make any major life changes
for at least 6 to 9 months after death
just don't give it to the parents yeah
no it's it's not theirs it's not what he
I really don't think that's what the
husband would have wanted and that's
what I would just say I'd be I would
literally be like I don't like the fact
that like this decision is put in my
hands because I don't like that I'm
holding back something that you guys
really want however I know it's not what
he wants yeah and if I thought even the
slightest bit it that it was what he
would want then this would be a
different story but I'm so confident
that it's not so like I don't want to
feel like the villain here
but I am the one who is able to legally
call the shots and this is just what I
think is right exactly legality is also
a very important point in this because
depending on the paperwork that they
filed when they did do the sperm
donation slaving it depending on what
state apparently it's a big thing so one
of the top comments is not the [__]
though this though the decision may not
actually be yours to make anyways if you
contact the sperm bank where it's frozen
they may likely have procedures on what
happens in the situations of the donor's
death there may be terms that he agreed
to in the paperwork that may State
ownership transfers to yourself or it
may state that the sample is destroyed
contact them and see what they say
though if ownership is now yours I don't
blame you at all for saying no op
replies ownership is mine
and someone comments back you are so
selfish and she goes for the legal
ownership passing to me after his death
question mark and the person literally
responds back everything is me me
me okay this woman just lost her [__]
husband wow this is where I get mad of
people being able to be anonymous on the
internet because what a godamn troll
literally yeah I I think was I I was
saying this D Morgan right we've talked
about this a lot yeah I I think that it
should be outlawed that people are able
to just create all these different
usernames and just be trolls on the
internet like if you want to say what
you want to say then have a face and a
name to it you know like I think that's
totally fine to express yourself and the
freedom of speech and everything but it
is so it's gotten so toxic and dangerous
the fact that people can just hide
behind these like I love CutiePie 563
and say evil things to people like that
is so wrong so I don't know it says a
lot about the people that do do that it
says a lot that you feel like you
there's a reason you're hiding behind
some fake little name there's a reason
there's clearly a reason you're a coward
and and they have nothing better to do
you're being cruel for the sake of being
cruel
because what is this going to get you
who is this going to benefit you are
being cruel for whatever malicious
reason that is oh they're just taking
out
whatever like frustrations or whatever
the [__] they have to everyone's
fighting their own battles and yeah it
could be it could be an outlet um wait
sorry Morgan could I interject for a
second yeah so I I'm just thinking that
um when you talked about the adoption
thing and you're like even like people
like you know like are always wondering
and stuff like that I'm going to
actually what I was going to add to that
is I was going to say hey I'm actually
going to phone a friend for a part of
this and I'm going to reach out to my
roommate Aeron Cella and have her
interject on this story but no but like
what I wanted to say is that because
we're talking about like should there be
a child be brought into this world or
not yeah then I think people who are
adopted are going to be like what so I
don't know who my parents are and so I
shouldn't have been brought into this
world I just think they're going to make
that parallel you know what I'm say
what do you think Justin I didn't get
that much of a Vibe
because at the same time when you're
talking about like babies that weren't
planned it's like that's what you say
about yourself all the time oh I am
literally an I am an oops baby 100% I
too actually well actually my mom is
which makes me like technically one I
think it was super valid because my ex
was I think technically adopted but she
knew her biological dad but didn't know
her biological mom at all or something
and I think everything she said was very
on point it was on point with what she
experienced and kind of that so there
was nothing that stuck out to me where
I'm like o okay that's fine I was just
saying because we're talking about the
concept of bringing a life into the
world or not I'm just I could see that
PE like I could just see people making
this parallel of being like wait so you
don't think I should have been brought
in the world just because I'm [__] up
over the fact I don't know who my
parents are biological you know what I'm
saying like and we can I think it would
be a point to like we can add this in
because I think this is very important
to have I'm going off of like I had a
college roommate that was adopted and
I've had other friends that were
adoptive and they are very very happy
they're there right they're very yeah
thankful for their adoptive parents they
love their adoptive parents they have a
great relationship with them but I've
also heard the opposite where people's
adoptive parents haven't been great but
from my experience no matter how great
the relationship is with the adoptive
parents my friends that have been
adoptive have always like had this
yearning to find their birth mom or find
their birth parents and I just think
it's like this kind of like it's just
this innate nature to like either
whether it's like know where you come
from know who you are a part of I don't
know I don't I don't know personally but
I just think it's a conversation to be
had and I think I will include because I
in my head when we were recording that
segment I was like I'm going to send her
the story and be like hey I know you're
adoptive I know you have a great
relationship with your birth parents
I'll let Aaron tell it if like start
crying H so it's so tough like this [__]
just [__] hits me but I'll let Aaron
tell it if she's willing um but Aaron
like kind of went through that
experience so we're going to phone a
friend I know [__] well I'd for sure
have that I would for sure have that
yearning yeah put yourself in that
situation you'd be like and and like I
said I I know way like Morgan I know
your heart and I know everything you're
saying I totally was like on board with
what you're saying I just know that we
we get so sick of people like making
assumptions and so I was just trying to
be like it's good to clarify so yeah if
um if you tune in to the YouTube version
I'll pH a friend I have no doubt she'll
respond uh so that'll be on the YouTube
version and here's where I'm going to
cut so I can get my [__]
together e
so I think we covered everything with
that one I think thank you for bringing
that up I I obviously don't want people
that are adopted to feel like they're
any less or shouldn't be here because I
think that that's definitely important
to to make that's what you saying it's
not what I was saying but I think it's
very easy to when you feel personal
about something to kind of infer I think
it's really easy to like misinterpret
things and so I don't I don't want there
to be any misinterpretation like a child
that's adoption adopted is just as
valuable and their life is just as
important and are like I just don't want
anything negative inferred from that I'm
just saying like in this
situation I think it is
unfair this it's just sperm it's not
even a child it's not like it's
inseminated eggs it is purely sperm yeah
which like how many how how many seeds
have been flushed swallowed or thrown
away yeah this is just sperm this is not
a baby wiped wiped WIP wiped tow towel
time towel time so I I'm glad you
brought that up because now we can
include it and just feel like all of our
boxes were were checked in
let me just shut the [__] up someone
else want to
read [__] I don't know if I'd be a good
reader well I kind of like it I honestly
thought that reading would be way more
smooth but then I remembered that I have
like like reading
anxiety same where it's like whenever
people would popcorn me poporn class I'd
be like no oh I Love Popcorn shoot me
shoot me I love pocor I like it's like I
know how to read but it's just like the
the uation of my voice and like when
when commas come and I don't see them
and they all of a sudden they're there
and I'm just like I pause and then that
stuff just doesn't bother me yeah it's
all well with that being said here you
go really yeah we're going to pass it
down the line what you're going to
popcorn me that's [__] up I just told
you my Trauma from grade
school all right let's let the real show
begin I needed a break after that last
one it was intense so we have a lot of
awards on this
one am I the [__] for not taking my
husband to my brother-in-law's funeral
after he went against my sister's
wishes my sister's husband was sick for
over 6 months in the past couple of
months he got worse they have two kids
nephew four and niece 6 I agreed to take
the kids in to look after them and help
my sister focus on her husband a week
ago I got a call at 650 from my sister
crying telling me her husband had just
passed away it was so devastating I was
still in bed when I got the news I
checked on the kids and they were asleep
I had to go see my sister and be with
her I asked my husband to keep an eye on
the kids and warned him not to tell them
about their father's passing till their
mom got there and could tell them
herself in her own way since she made me
promise to wait till she left them
herself he nodded but said telling them
the sooner the better I told him it was
none of his business and he needed to
respect their mother's wish he said I
could go and he'd watch the
kids an hour later my phone rang while I
was with my sister and it was my husband
telling me to get home ASAP because the
kids had a breakdown after he told them
their father passed I was dumbfounded
and so so mad and helpless I asked why
he told them but I couldn't hear his
reply because the kids were crying
loudly in the background their mother
heard and figured they found out she
told me to drive her to see them I
apologized for what my husband did but
she didn't respond we got home and it
was a mess my heart sank seeing the kids
crying for their dad like that their mom
took them inside the room and shut the
door I lost it on my husband and he said
he didn't want to say anything even made
them breakfast but when he heard the
kids talk about what they were going to
do when they when they see their dad he
felt the urge to tell them I yell yelled
at him for going against my sister's
wishes he apologized to my sister but
she said she doesn't want to see him
because the kids stopped talking from
their
trauma he wanted to go to the funeral
but I told him my sister doesn't want to
see him and I'm respecting her wish he
got upset saying I excluded him from
family events which was unfair and flat
out Petty he said he couldn't help it so
I shouldn't hold him accountable because
it just
happened but I felt ashamed and a major
let down from my sister because she
stated her wishes and he didn't respect
them um he's an [__] huge [__] I
want to cry thinking about that like if
I was a mother
and those were my wishes that I wanted
to be the one to tell my kids
that that's just why like I they're
going to be traumatized why like why did
he think that was his right well it was
so explicitly like she made it so clear
beforehand like he's trying to be like
no they need to know now they don't
they're when a kid is that little
they're going to remember who they were
with and how they were
told oh I just like just picture them
picture them over
breakfast I just can't wait until dad's
not sick and we can go to the lake and
he goes well actually your dad died this
morning yeah literally he would decide
you're not going to be going to the lake
how could he decide that was his
responsibility in his place like that is
so sad no and then him being like you
excluded me from a family thing you
[__] lost any rights to be around
that family the minute that you [__]
their life upside down you went against
her
wishes you ruined those
kids moment of grief that they should
have shared with their mom their mom
their mom should have been there the
fact that they found out and they're
Bing without their mom there that makes
me sick to my stach young how old are
they again four and six and six they're
babies they're [__] babies I they
don't know what's going on they need be
with this person what what was wrong
with him like if it was if it wasn't
made clear beforehand I would be like it
was a mistake like he thought he was
doing the right thing he's being honest
but it was very clear before don't tell
them what did he say to he was like he
literally was like I feel like they need
to know well it I feel like I'm such I
feel like I'm just the biggest trust guy
ever because all of these issues I
always go to trust but from you
literally now can't trust him you asked
him to do something and you trusted him
to not do something and it's a huge
thing that's and especially when we're
talking about like how much childhood
moments like that really make an impact
on you as a human they shape us they
really do
those things are huge like huge and yes
I I I have faith that the kids will be
able to you know get over that and live
a happy life but I mean that that moment
obviously it's going to take a lot to
like handle the fact that their dad
passed away but like therapy but hearing
it from him I'm sure that they'll get
you know they'll move on from it but
that he just added a difficulty that was
so unnecessary and not his place and so
[__] up this like makes me scared to
let anyone watch my kids honestly well
it kind of feels like he didn't care
exactly it feels like it didn't feel
that big to him where he just like oh
guess what or like it was exciting news
that he wanted to be the one to like
break it yeah it's very weird I I would
be the exact same way if I was that
person's significant other I would be
like I don't know if I want you to
around any of these people anymore and I
don't even know if I want to be around
you because like that that was a huge
breach that you did that wasn't
something small no and I'm I know I'm
quick to be like divorce break up but
this like our first review in the
podcast deal though but these girls just
say divorce and we're like well yeah
we're not married so it's easy and this
is not my relationship so obviously I'm
not attached to it yeah but I just look
at this as if my partner would have
violated my trust gone against my wishes
disrespected me disrespected my family
traumatized my niece and nephew I just
like I look at all this and I'm like add
all this combined and then the fact he's
whimpering and oh now he's the victim
also him being like you're excluding me
from a family event this is [__] a
funeral this is not a [__] holiday
party celebration yeah you're being
excluded from a funeral because you just
ruined that kid those kids grieving
process he's playing victim I'm looking
at this person and I'm like
let's add up all the reasons why you're
an [__] yeah and I'm like do I want
to be with this
person yeah so it's it reminds me of the
the lady who threw away all the pictures
of the late
mom he ruined this like it's the same
[__] and I I watch episode yet I look at
how traumatic death is like I I'm so
[__] in the head like I'm so scared of
losing my dad that I literally go and
check and make sure he's
breathing when I wake up in the morning
and he's not gone before me like I'm
terrorized of losing a parent so like I
can't even imagine these four and
5-year-old kids who are just like just
beginning their little lives and
just [__] absolute [__] D yeah I
completely agree he's the [__] she is
not the [__] for not taking him to
the funeral which leads into the
actually there was a mod uh that
stickied the comment so it's at the top
yeah saying all right folks is that time
of day again we remind you to be civil
yeah good luck on this one so this one
got pretty heated uh top comment has a
lot of
awards uh not the [__] I was
babysitting for a family friend while
they were at the hospital saying goodbye
to their other child oh I knew that
their son had died but I kept my mouth
shut and loved on their daughter who was
talking about going to see her brother
brother until they got home because it
was we both going to cry because it was
1 million per not my place to say
anything didn't even cross my mind to
tell her even though I had to leave the
room a few times to wipe my eyes and
regain
composure yeah
okay so but yeah it's it's
100% not your [__] place to tell he's
an adult if you need to go in the other
room and step back like yeah you just
lost your brother in
yeah step back like step back this is
not your place though I don't understand
in what rational mind MH well and this
is interesting exactly children that
young are easily distracted as well he
really could have thrown on the TV for a
few hours until their mom came no he
totally wanted to hurt those kids by
telling them they were distracted it
almost seems like he wanted to just like
have the spotlight like yes like have
the power like just like oh I know this
news I'm going to let you guys know like
I want to be the first to let you like I
don't know but like it makes me so sick
he's unhinged and again again obviously
I don't know like we're not hearing him
talk we are not hearing like his
situation but like from what we do know
this is sick it makes me so sad and I
get every situation is so subjected to
the person that experiences it like
obviously op writing in is the wife in
the situation but there's very objective
information here it was expressly said
don't tell the kids and he still went
against that and told the kids so no
matter what else went on in this
situation he had one [__] one [__]
assignment youd one job he did not
understand the assignment well and the
other way to think about it that you
kind of lightly touched on is now the
kids forever have this memory with him
these kids have not spoken that's the
whole reason he's not invited in the
funeral too like one he disobeyed all
guidelines did not understand the
assignment but these kids have now gone
like mute right they did they did write
that that they haven't been talking they
haven't been talking these kids have now
because of this trauma and this sadness
have decided not to talk yeah the kids
stop talking from their
trauma it makes me so sick and I think
the reason it makes me so so so sick is
that I'm assuming assing that this guy
is like very like in his right mind and
very level noral and like not on does
not have any diagnosis is just a normal
dude not taking drugs like not like out
of this world like I'm assuming these
things and so it just makes me so sick
because I'm like who in their rational
right mind like who do you think you are
well and for kids this young entitlement
but kids this young to stop
talking four and five four and six like
make that making that choice at that age
to be like well I just if someone random
like to me like random I not super
random but like that's just not my my
home is telling me that someone that I
love most in the entire universe you
also like don't believe it there's it's
just so sickening to me like it wasn't
his place like I want to scream at this
man I want to kill
him I think there's something though
where the younger you are that trauma
occurs the more likely you are to
actually stop talking and this is
something I definitely I'm going to fact
check I like really want to look this up
where um to make sure like this is
actually a thing but I think the younger
trauma happens that the more likely
someone is to like stop talking or shut
down interesting I just need to fact
check that's interesting though cuz I my
first thought was that the younger you
are the more likely you would be to
continually just ask questions and try
to understand because you've never
experienced these
Concepts and I think it's like exactly
what you're saying but flip it you've
never experienced these Concepts so you
don't know how to deal with it so you
shut down but I also think though too at
an older age you could shut down just
because you do understand what has truly
happened and you just shut down I don't
know it's called selective mutism
and obviously this is like a very
specific
circumstance so I'm not even sure if I'm
going to find anything like directly on
this yeah
so there's not a lot on this but there's
so this one quote there's also a
misconception that kids who can't speak
in some settings have been traumatized
in fact kids who become mute after a
traumatic experience are typically mute
in all situations not specific social
environments so these kids literally
could be
affected pretty greatly in all areas of
their life going forward because of the
fact that this man took it into his own
hands and thought it was his [__] job
his due diligence to tell these poor
children makes me so
mad yeah there's not a lot on this
either like selective mutism after
trauma there's
not I wish people a lot on it there's so
many things through growing up that I
now look back and I'm like I learned so
much in school about things that are
just not relevant to me today and I
don't regret learning those things cuz I
think they help with your brain like
developing and understanding just I
don't I don't even know but but what
makes me mad is that there's so many
things that we could learn I I still
feel like there should be more
communication for people to really
understand how these things can have an
impact because I don't know I think that
even like with myself like my mom loves
me so much and I love my mom so much and
then I still think some of these things
that happen like in my childhood like
where you know she wasn't trying to be
mean at all like or bad or anything like
she's a great mom to me but I think that
some of these things have an impact on
who I am 100% And like we just
don't know yeah no one knows that like
well it's it's nature versus nurture we
are we are a sum of our environment I
think biology plays a big part but I
also think we are heavily shaped by our
experiences yeah and I started realizing
more and more like these certain
instances as a kid I'm starting to
remember these times where it's like no
one was outright like trying to like
hurt me or be mean to me but these
things made me feel a certain way that
has like shaped who I am now yeah it's
just crazy I don't know I just think it
should be more of a topic so back to the
story there's not a update uh did you
realize this was posted one day ago no
but I did look for the update yeah this
was posted one day ago so very update to
come very very fresh
we will keep our eyes peeled for an
update op only replies to one
comment and it is this comment says not
the [__] at allll do not take the
responsibility of your spouse's acts on
yourself you clearly express your
sister's wishes he made the choice to go
directly against them your sister had
every right to not want contact at all
with him after that who knows how the
kids would have responded Ed or been
more traumatized seeing him
again you are not petty you're trying to
love and respect and support your sister
in her time of grief and op goes yes I
agree but he's been giving me grief
about how harsh I was towards him and
that I should have let him attend the
funeral with me completely ignoring the
fact he went against my sister's wishes
and she rightfully wants some space from
him someone else replies to op and goes
it's not about you none of this is about
you on repeat until he gets
it and someone replies back to that
that's what I was going to say tell him
quote this is not about you or any of
your feelings this is about sister and
her kids that's it he made a choice and
this is the outcome of his very selfish
Choice yes mhm yes I
honestly I've we've read the most crazy
stories I've listened to the most crazy
stories on this podcast but this like I
genuinely don't think I would ever want
to see him again if I was if I was the
parent of these kids I don't think I
would I don't think I would forgive him
like obviously he could do things to
like I you know I'm not going to be he
could try to redeem himself he could try
to redeem himself but like as of how
acting right now I don't ever see myself
wanting to be around this man you'll
never trust you'll never trust no but
like him gaslighting her you're being
petty you're being petty this is a petty
problem no Petty problems are not this
this is life altering for multiple
people this is not
Petty I think I know this sounds kind of
crazy but I think one of the only things
I'd be thinking about why I would want
to have a relationship with with him is
some familiarity for my kids almost like
like the person who told you this news
is in our life and their family like I
don't I don't know if that makes sense
but like that would be like to try to
lessen the severity exactly like that
would be my one consideration cuz if we
you never see him again it's a random
man who just told you this news yeah but
I also think the fact that the kids are
already so traumatized like this has
already been their Uncle for the time
they've probably been born like I don't
know if op ever says how long they've
been
married um yeah no I'm just saying
that's like my one thing that I would be
like cuz otherwise I would be like I
don't want to see this man again the
only way I would consider it is if he
really for that reason to try to like to
try to lessen the severity of the
situation I get that it doesn't mention
how long they've been married so we
don't know that but I think the fact
that these kids were so traumatized by
him telling them that they went
selectively mute kind of already says
like it doesn't I don't I don't think
him being included is going to make the
situation better because if he was
already a part of the family and
included in a way like you know what I'm
saying like where it's like yeah he
already burned the bridge like there's
not anything that's going to lessen the
severity of the situation
because he's not the person that should
have told them mhm I think uh We've
burned the bridge on this one and he's
gone yep it would be really hard for me
as how do you move on as the as the what
or if I was you know as like whoever I
am as my partner
and my
sister I it would constantly put me in a
really uncomfortable place where I'm I
know where like I side with I side with
my sister and not because she's my
sister but because of the situation so
it would just be so hard like I would
just be like every time I'd go to a
family thing I remember you were a
[__] [__] yeah
it would just be hard like I I'm not
saying they can't get through it but
like it' be really hard for
me I don't know we'll we'll look out for
the update on this
one but can't believe that you said that
was just a day ago one day ago wow I
hopped on that one real fast I don't
know why it always like blows my mind
when these things are recent yeah
speaking of recent this one was N9 days
ago
popcorn popcorn who you me am I the
[__] for cleaning out the fridge
without telling my
husband what do you guys think finally
like a happy kind of one lighthearted
unhinge do we know what DH is doing
husband I believe okay my DH brought
home a metal box that he checks on often
during the day when it's in the fridge
when asked about it he said it contained
freshly pickled olives his friend Jason
got from his uncle's farm and wanted DH
to keep till he gets back from his
business trip I had no problem with him
keeping it safe at the bottom of the
fridge DH always asked me to be cautious
with the box and not open it as it'd be
rude to touch other people's
stuff yesterday I decided to clean out
the fridge which took me about two two
hours from unplugging the fridge
emptying all of the items grocery
vegetables containers and washing and
cleaning out the inside of it letting it
settle before plugging it in again I
took the Box my husband brought out of
the fridge and placed it on the kitchen
island alongside the containers while I
was working I received a video call Via
WhatsApp for my husband while at work
feeling bored asking what I was doing I
showed him I was cleaning out the fridge
and he suddenly freaked out and asked
about the metal
box I was confused so I told him to calm
down and I showed him where the box was
he got mad telling me I should not have
cleaned out the fridge nor even touched
the box without telling him I again
tried to ask asked him to calm down as I
saw no big deal about it his precious
box was safe and sound but he went on a
Rand about how the Box needed to be put
back inside the fridge ASAP and told me
to plug the fridge in right then but I
couldn't because it was still wet and I
wasn't finished cleaning the other
parts apparently I pissed him off by
stalling and he hung up and 30 minutes
later he came home and pitched a hissy
fit saying I should have picked a time
where he was home to clean out the
fridge so he could take the box
somewhere else to keep it cool I said so
what it was sitting out of the fridge
for barely 2 hours and olives can stand
being outside the fridge for a longer
period he said I don't get it and took
the box and wanted to leave with it I
asked where he was taking it and he said
he needed to go back to work and had no
time to explain I Shrugged this whole
thing off but he came back with it in
the evening and put it inside the fridge
then complained about me cleaning the
fridge without telling him and acting
dismissive of his opinions I argued that
what opinions could he have on cleaning
out the fridge he argued back saying he
promised Jason he'd keep his olives in
good condition and I should have just
told him end of
story I wonder if I messed up he usually
doesn't get that mad unless I've messed
up and I think that I
have is that the end um so what the [__]
is in the Box I'm picturing body parts
save that it I'm picturing body parts I
was going to say what body parts are in
this I'm over here thinking like
sperm from more other story I'm sperms
no sperm has sperm sperm has to be kept
in a Freez no I know that it doesn't
make sense but like that's just where my
like where where I'm at right now I'm
dead ass I'm like what body parts is
this yeah like who freaks the [__] out
that they and he checks he checks the
boxes the Box multiple times a day yeah
but isn't it like the movie Rat Race
where they're trying to keep that heart
cool enough to make it all the way
through the whole movie and get I forgot
that movie existed oh my God I don't
know if I've seen it oh this is a first
takes place in Minnesota doesn't it some
I I I don't know that much about all I
know is there's some heart in some like
makeshift cooler and they're trying to
keep it alive I know it sounds really
really familiar to where I feel like
I've probably seen it but I'm not sure
but why is he checking a box of Olives
multiple times a day cuz they're
precious why is he concerned about the
olives being outside of a fridge no one
would leave work early for olives I'm
sorry that's what I'm saying also like I
like Justin always is like very
concerned about food being left on the
counter and like getting food poisoning
and the like when I've been to like
parties and there's a chutery board with
olives on it like that [__] sits out for
like 6 hours I would get worried about
olives my Mom leaves pizzas out for like
3 days noan Morgan leaves chicken out
like all day and that [__] is warm
sitting on the counter I'm like dude I'm
not about to eat this and she'll cook it
up be like it's fine we're good here
here is my theory think about a grad
school high school my grad party the
chicken had a little heater under it and
it was heated I don't leave chicken out
for that long but I don't think that was
for safety reasons I think that was like
for yeah I think it's both it no I think
it was for more like let's not have
people equ you can't mess with that [__]
though you cannot I've been on the bad
end of that I have two but I think well
you also have a really sensitive stomach
so yes anyone would be sensitive to that
[__] eoli coming up in there anyone's
going to be messed up I think you can
leave food out for a lot longer than a
lot of people think is what I'm going to
say so like I think about the grad
school rule like if I left this out at a
grad school party right now could I eat
it in 6 hours yeah yeah okay I'm going
to eat it like I don't know like I've
forgotten Pizza on my counter drunkenly
one night and I eat it next night for
dinner if I left a Chick-fil-A sandwich
out overnight I'd eat it the next day
you bet I'm eating that
those nuggets that Chick-fil-A sauce
let's go mhm those aren't olives in that
box raw raw chicken that's different raw
chicken is to she'll leave raw chicken
out for 2 weeks and be like tastes good
and eat it raw no and then she'll be
like think about gr
parties you are just lying no I deal
with this almost on a daily basis you
are lying like you think this chicken's
good oh yeah it's fine you're a [__]
liar though because you brought [__]
Co chicken over and you go oh I think it
might be still good and you open up and
I smell it I go no throw it away I don't
see my nose growing Morgan the
hero I'm not
Pinocchio no I'm not Pinocchio you guys
I'm Pinocchio not not because I'm lying
but because you guys like two days ago
told you to throw that chicken away two
days ago I discovered a Snapchat filter
that makes you Pinocchio and I was like
I don't know why this makes me feel like
oh I sent that to her I was like I have
a dick on my nose and I I'm not mad
about it it flops all around yeah it was
very flert clip of me that I sent to
Morgan you need to redo it I didn't save
you guys I saved mine too I'll send them
to
you so back to this front there's
definitely body parts in there um
there's something crazy this is not
olives in this box but like why would
why would they keep body parts like it's
kidneys but then why would
okay what are the
updates so this is this is a husband
like why would you not tell like I'm
sorry boys don't tell anything boys keep
secrets is that [__] true Justin I
don't know do you think your kind
[__] does that it's [__] I feel
attacked um okay so edit first of all
yes I'm aware that DH is overprotective
of his box but he always
but box but he always acts like that
whenever someone asks him to keep
something safe for him like furniture or
car parts and second of
all so this is a regular occurrence keep
this car part safe for me don't let an
atomic bomb go off and destroy it please
watch my
chair I mean this is what I have to deal
with with my boyfriend like all of his
stuff is like so sacred like I didn't
realize that like my fingerprints on his
drawers are going to like that's weird
he's being OCD the fact that multiple
people are reaching out and dropping
items off at his house to keep safe oh
drug
dealer he has drugs in the furniture
what so take a take a peek at this chair
right here see the bottom of the chair
how the bottom lining is like sagging a
little bit okay there's drugs in there
there's drugs in there you got to put
that chair in the fridge wait the minute
you said that I go that's where you
would sew in drugs I've seen on Tik Tok
you guys this is so wild but I've seen
on Tik Tok videos of semi-truck drivers
or Smugglers smuggling [__] in I think
you're talking about cartel talk oh I'm
on that too I see the planes all the
time I see the planes I see cartel talk
all the time but I I see all this stuff
where people are smuggling I see cartel
talk whatever it is where they literally
have like a truck full of wood
and then if you pick up a section of the
wood there's [__] it's lined with
cocaine oh yeah I used to watch live PD
and they'd put in all the cars
compartments tires and everything I
exactly and so I'm like chairs car parts
a
box either way there's not [__]
olives in there would you have not
opened the box I would have opened the
box would you open the bo open the box I
would open the box the minute it got in
my pres so is op crazy for not opening
the box yes yes the minute he flipped
out on FaceTime the minute he was like
I'm coming home from work don't touch
the box or whatever he said or you been
in there I would have Box open and you
would have seen all the raw oliv you
guys I'm so [__] annoying I will
Google the movie spoilers when I'm in
the middle of the movie she will it's
[__] up I want to know and I'm
literally and she and she we'll watch a
movie together and then all of a sudden
she gets her phone out and she's and
then I look over her go don't do it and
she goes and smiles and I'm like you
know you know I'm like don't you dare
tell me she I don't tell you though you
you have
no you kind of insinuate there's some
there's something in the look of your
eyes that I instantly know the rest of
the movie exct I can't handle what my
eyes do then stop Googling it I have to
know I have to know I was just going to
say I have to know oh my god um no I I
have I actually the worst part about
this story is that I've taken on your
bad habits and I started doing that and
I like I don't do that with everything
what's the point of watching the movie I
know I don't do that with everything I
do that with series I do it with series
when I'm just like I am not about to
have anxiety for the next like 10
episodes that's what it
is so like I just need to know like did
you actually die or like are you coming
back to life like I just let's get this
out of the way because I don't want to
mourn you for 10 episodes and you come
back to life and I don't I haven't
regretted it I think that's why Game of
Thrones ending was so heartbreaking for
me because I didn't know what was coming
oh my God okay they ruined it no y'all
you guys are crazy but we're not GNA go
down that rabbit hole wait okay so
before no what I do want to say though
actually from high school one of my best
friends in high school her dad he was
like so nerdy so sweet they're all quiet
drug deer like um no and and like and
like his mom her mom and her dad were
married or are still married like
sweetest couple ever so cute whatever he
literally grew weed in their Bas so a
drug dealer and well I don't know if he
was a drug dealer or if he just like it
was a passion or like a hobby but if
it's in Minnesota it's illegal exactly
drug deal and especially what was this
like how many years ago was this like
high school you graduated high school in
2011 so you were ages 20 we don't need
to talk about these things yeah you're
right makes me feel way too old okay
back to the story okay so edit first of
all I'm aware that DH is acting
overproductive of the box but he always
acts like that whenever someone comes
over and ask them to keep an item safe
like Furniture car parts and second of
all no I haven't seen those olives
myself and I haven't opened the box
because I didn't even think I had to but
DH tends to be overprotective of his
friends belongings so I didn't give it
much thought how another edit how do you
resist because many were wondering yes I
unplugged the fridge before cleaning out
since I did Heavy cleaning you can see
that is a common method just Google it
if you're curious I do it all the time
and to give give some info the metal box
does look like a container of some sort
but DH calls it box so I didn't think
much different I don't give a [__] about
how you unplugged the fridge I want to
know what's in the box so I think that
the edits are clearly responding to the
comments which we don't know what they
are yet so go look at her um account and
see if there's an update someone goes
question what does your husband do for
work San
construction garbage
Transportation op replies back no he
works at a marketing company as an
assistant and is a Serial Killer
Dexter Dexter someone replies back
please open the box yes although I am
sure he will have changed whatever was
on the inside when he took the box with
him [__] someone go I think she opened
the box and he was standing in the
doorway that's what I'll continue to
think until she says anything else and
that had better be her telling us what's
in the box or I will lose my mind
someone goes marketing company Stand
Down everyone it's just
cocaine yeah true um which I would not
be surprised if it's
drugs in the fridge yeah exactly why
would you freak out about cocaine not
being in the fridge like what needs to
be in the fridge it's got to be a lot of
cocaine like what if it's like a
$100,000 worth need be in theid [__]
ain't in the fridge when it's coming in
the planes and [__] no chance no no no
no but I I'm sure like for him it's just
like if it's in the fridge don't it I
know where it is don't touch it cuz he
doesn't want her to open it up but he
freaked out about her unplugging the
fridge don't even bring it home yeah he
was he was like you unplugged the fridge
I know which also like I guess if it was
cocaine and you didn't want your wife to
find it why not like stick it under
anywhere else under your bed there has
to be something else what else needs to
be in the face or is just [__] nuts
about protecting other people's [__]
like oh my God Morgan's like take these
strawberries I'll eat them in a couple
days and I'm just like no matter what
I'm going in from the studio every 5
minutes to make sure that the fridge is
those are fing
stupid yeah another comment info have
you actually confirmed that it is really
olives in there because it's all kind of
sounds suspicious no because why would I
since husband said it contained olives
honestly I don't know why some people
think this is weird husband can be a
little too dramatic and overprotective
of others belongings and since it
belongs to his friend then why bother
looking inside it's not like he took it
from a stranger what's wrong with her
she's very trusting I'm pissed so she
got literally like almost a thousand
down votes on that comment good and
someone replies back and goes seriously
stop whatever you're doing and go look
in that box and if you're [__] posting
for fun I don't care pretend you open
the box and make up something good yeah
God this is [__] crazy like what's in
the box I what just makes me mad is that
she's like why are you going to Reddit
and asking people for their advice and
you're not realizing the fact that this
is really questionable hi Holly like
this is so questionable like what if
you're if you if anyone's going to freak
out that much about something in a
secret box and you were like there's
something bad in box why would I look
like yeah no one drives home from work
to take the box with them back to work
and then brings the box back home at the
end of the day with olives for real it's
a lot what kind of Olives are they are
are they [__] gold I don't care if
they're imported from Italy with like
[__] magical truffles on them no one
does that well that maybe maybe they've
been maybe they've been ripened for 100
years or not ripened what's it called
what's it called fermented yeah that is
true pickled pickled pickled pickled
pickled fermented I think pickled they
did say pickled for 100 years maybe
that's
it but still I was still the box like
out let's go with that so we all can
just sleep tonight and not be I don't
know how you can like literally be that
uncrazy
to like not look in the box I would have
looked in the box from the GetGo I would
have said you're not keeping your
friend's box in our fridge unless I know
exactly same I'll get my own fridge
there's not a goddamn chance I would
have let that box come in my fridge
without knowing what's inside is this
the end you just close your computer I
kind of like that though it's like a mic
drop everyone's going to be left
wondering what is in the Box mhm I think
this is a good this is a good point to
end I think unhinged might have to come
in 2.0 version down the road because I
got a I got a lot saved in this little
magical computer of
mine but how did you feel you've been
wanting
crazy I really enjoyed this
conversation it's pretty good we cried
we laughed we did roller coaster we did
cry and we did laugh this was truly a
roller coaster of emotions yeah I think
that's like one thing that's really
great about this show is that we are
very authentic M to ourselves and our
emotions and crying is okay yeah I
agree I really don't have anything else
to say on this one except that unhinged
2.0 will be coming down the road at some
point that's all we have for you guys on
this episode of two hot takes and until
next time this was the best day
ever until next time until next time bye
guys adios
[Music]